In this video, I will introduce you to the main function of the 2025.2 version, the paper editor, to help you improve the product design to a new level.
Now you can directly define the structure of the paper in the 3D project, implement editing and accurately simulate the shrinkage effect, and the design experience is fully upgraded.
Let's take a closer look at the workflow.
First, select a fabric in the object window.
In the property editor, change the material type to a wool product.
In the 2025.2 version, you can see a new needle ball icon.
Open the paper editor.
Click to open the editor.
The window of the paper editor will appear in the 2D window.
You can click on the option card at the bottom to switch.
It is very easy to guide the draft.
You can use a space similar to the window in the 3D window to adjust the draft in the editor.
Press the middle key and move the mouse wheel to parallel the draft.
Rotate the middle key wheel to enlarge and shrink the draft.
Press the mouse right key and move the mouse right key.
You can rotate the draft around the center freely.
Hold the mouse wheel fleshin to make time- catches.
Use the mouse wheel sandwich to expand the left and right sizes.
Pinch it further to load the whole screen.
Press the switch to switch to any system mode.
Press the shortcut button, you can switch to the desired preset view at any time.
You can use three types of sand line display to check the paper.
Thick sand line shows the actual thickness and pure color.
Thin sand line automatically displays the structure of the needle.
To enhance the visibility of the needle structure.
The color of the thread is used in a random way.
Each line uses a color randomly.
So you can easily check the thread structure.
Next is the core setting.
Here you can set the size of the piece of paper and the final output size.
To set the specific data of the piece of paper, please enter the number of the sample cycle in the direction of the thread density.
Then enter the number of the sample cycle in the direction of the thread density.
Then enter the number of時 math in the direction of the thread density.
P grupp and get back on track.
Now enter the number of the sample cycle.
Then enter the number of the sample cycle in the direction of the thread density.
Then enter the data of the number of hours by the signal type as you see on the screen in starburg.
Next, you can set the line thickness in the line thickness of mm and adjust the density of the line circle.
Click on the icon to see more evidence options.
The link shows the automatic measurement value of the current result.
Or you can click to cancel the link.
To enter the final piece size after shrink, such as the number of rows per inch, the number of rows per inch and the thickness of the fabric.
Change the line thickness.
The line circle density adjusts the number of rows per inch.
The number of rows per inch.
After the thickness of the fabric is set, the real sample will be automatically updated.
Please note that you do not need to click the reset piece button.
If you want to understand the definition of the setting, you can stop the mouse on the setting.
Check the tool tips.
Start editing.
You can select the needle type from the menu on the right.
Or use the shortcut key.
Support four options.
Including the front needle bed, the shortcut key is Q.
The back needle bed, the shortcut key is W.
The front needle bed is not edited, the shortcut key is 1, and the front loop needle is the back line.
And the back needle bed is not edited, the shortcut key is 2, and the back loop needle is the front line.
Then you can click and drag the piece.
Do real needle editing.
After the sample design is completed.
Press the simulation button or press the control key.
You can use your evidence and custom setting application to shrink the effect.
Now you can see that the piece structure presents a curve due to shrink.
You can continue to edit during simulation activation.
Also update the shrink effect.
Then press the simulation button or press the control key.
You can pause.
To apply your piece design to the costume.
Press the application button.
Use the result to 3D costume.
Or press the application and close.
Apply the result and close the editor.
If you just want to give up the change.
Please press cancel.
In the 3D window.
You can check the result.
And make further changes in the editor.
After the change.
Press the application button or the application and close.
The editor will add a new one.
This option is related to the evidence.
When the piece editor is opened.
The thread line is thin.
The number of rows per inch.
And the thickness of the fabric will be used.
To ensure that all changes are managed through the piece editor.
After closing the piece editor.
These options will be available again.
Allow you to make further adjustments.
And check the 3D effect immediately.
Next.
You can adjust the thread line settings in the property editor.
Such as the color of the thread line.
And the color of the bone thread.
After completion.
You can save this fabric.
For the next application.
And you can use the seamless division function.
More flexible performance.
This step-by-step stitch change.
You can use the piece editor now.
Create more accurate.
More complex digital piece design.